Guide to the Manley H. Thompson Papers 1939-1998
University of Chicago Library
- Series VI: Writings by Others
  - Baum, Manfred: "The B-Deduction and the Refutation of Idealism" – Typescript Draft, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Beck, Lewis White: Walsh Remembrance, "Five Concepts of Freedom in Kant," Publisher's Notice, 1983-1986, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Brittan, Gordon G.: "Constructability and the World-Picture," "Theoretical Objects," "Kant's Two Grand Hypotheses" – Typescripts, Correspondence, Offprint, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Brittan, Gordon G: "The Kantian Foundations of Modern Science," Offprint and Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Brumbaugh, Robert: "The History and an Interpretation of the Text of Plato's Parmenides" – Typescript, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Brumbaugh, Robert: "Whitehead and a Committee," "Diction and Dialectic.. .," Forward to A. E. Taylor, Socrates – Photocopies, 1983, 1989, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Brumbaugh, Robert: "Digression and Dialogue: The Seventh Letter and Plato's Literary Form," "Doctrine and Dramatic Dates.. ." – Photocopies, 1988, undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Brumbaugh, Robert and Rulon Wells: "Yale's Plato Project," Brumbaugh and John P. Burnham: "Coins and Classical Philosophy," 1989, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Bubner, Rüdiger: "The Self-Referential Structure of Transcendental Arguments" – Typescript, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Burks, Arthur, "Logic, Learning, and Creativity in Evolution" – Typescript, Letter, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Corcoran, John: "Logical Structures of Ockham's Theory of Supposition," "Transcendental Idealism: the Dialectical Dimension" – Typescript, Offprint, Letter, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - de Pierris, Graciela: "Kant and Innatism," "Frege and Kant on A Priori Knowledge" – Typescripts, Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Donagan, Alan: "Berkeley's Theory of the Immediate Objects of Vision" (with comments), "Informed Consent in Therapy and Experimentation," 1974 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Eldridge, Richard: "Frege's Realist Theory of Knowledge.. ." Offprint, Letter, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Eldridge, Richard: "Literature and the Phenomenology of Moral Consciousness.. .," "The Normal and the Normative.. .," "Self-Understanding and Community in Wordsworth's Poetry," Baker and Hacker Reviews -- Offprints, Typescript, Letter, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Engstrom, Stephen: "The Concept of the Highest Good in Kant's Ethical Theory," "Conditioned Autonomy" – Typescript Drafts, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Engstrom, Stephen – "On the Traditional Doctrine that what is Desired.. .," "Kantian Universalization" – Typescripts, Correspondence, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Engstrom, Stephen: "The Objectives and the Structure of Kant's Transcendental Deduction," "The Transcendental Deduction and Skepticism" – Typescripts, Correspondence with Commentary, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Farrell, B. A.: "On the Design of a Conscious Device" – Offprint, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Field, Hartry: "Mental Representation" – Photocopy, Notes, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Fisch, Max: "The 'Proof' of Pragmatism," "Hegel and Peirce" – Typescripts, Correspondence, Offprint, 1972-1976 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Fisch, Max: "Peirce's General Theory of Signs," Peirce Review - Photocopies, circa 1976, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Fisch, Max: Presidential Address, "Peirce's and Husserl's Phenomenology.. .," Peirce Edition Preface – Typescripts, Offprint, 1979, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Fӧrster, Eckart – Kant's Opus Postumum – Correspondence, 1983-1988 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Fӧrster, Eckart – Kant's Opus Postumum – Introduction – Draft with Comments, circa 1988 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Fӧrster, Eckart and Michael Rosen – Kant's Opus Postumum (Translation) – Typescript [1 of 2], circa 1988 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Fӧrster, Eckart and Michael Rosen – Kant's Opus Postumum (Translation) – Typescript [2 of 2], circa 1988 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Fӧrster, Eckart: "Kant and Skepticism Concerning Metaphysics" – Draft and Correspondence, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Frede, Michael and Lorenz Krüger: "Über die Zuordnung der Quantitäten des Urteils.. ." – Photocopy and Thompson's Notes, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Friedman, Michael – "Kant's Theory of Geometry" – Conference Paper, Handout, Thompson's Response (Typescripts, Notes), undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Friedman, Michael – "Kant's Theory of Geometry" – Typescript Draft, Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Friedman, Michael: "Kant's Theory of Geometry" – Journal, Offprint, Photocopy, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Friedman, Michael: "Kant on the Foundations of Newtonian Science" – Typescript Draft, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Friedman, Michael: "Carnap's Aufbau Reconsidered," "Logical Truth and Analyticity in Carnap's Logical Syntax of Language" -- Typescript Drafts, 1984-1986 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Friedman, Michael: "The Metaphysical Foundations of Newtonian Science" – Typescript Drafts, Offprint, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Friedman, Michael: "Kant on Concepts and Intuitions in the Mathematical Sciences" – Typescripts, Notes, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Friedman, Michael: "Kant and Newton: Why Gravity is Essential to Matter," "observations on B40" (Response to Thompson) – Typescripts, 1987, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Friedman, Michael: "Kant on Space, the Understanding, and the Law of Gravitation: Prolegomena §38" – Typescript Draft, Handout, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Friedman, Michael: "On the Transition from the Metaphysical Foundations of Natural Science to Physics," "Kant on Causal Laws and the Foundations of Natural Science" – Typescripts, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Gadamer, Hans Georg – "The Philosophical Foundations of the Twentieth Century" – Photocopy, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Gewirth, Alan: "Economic Rights," "Moral Foundations of Civil Rights Law," "Ethical Universalism and Particularism" – Offprints, 1986-1988 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Gewirth, Alan: "Rights and Duties," "The Justification of Morality," "Human Rights and Conceptions of the Self" – Offprints, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Gewirth, Alan: "Die Rationalen Grundlagen der Ethik," "Private Philanthropy and Positive Rights, " "The Egoist's Objection," "Reason and Nuclear Deterrence," clipping, 1989, 1993, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Gewirth, Alan: Williams Review, "Why Rights are Indispensable," "The Problem of Specificity in Evolutionary Ethics" – Offprints, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Gewirth, Alan: "Can Any Final Ends be Rational?" "Common Morality and the Community of Rights," "Two Types of Cost-Benefit Analysis" – Offprints, 1991-1993, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Gewirth, Alan: "The Rationality of Reasonableness," "Human Dignity as the Basis of Rights," "Human Rights and Academic Freedom" –Offprints, 1983-1992 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Goldfarb, Warren – "I Want You to Bring Me a Slab.. ." 1983 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Gram, Moltke S.: "The Skeptical Attack on Substance: Kantian Answers," "What Kant Really Did to Idealism" – Offprints, 1981, undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Gram, Moltke S.: "Intellectual Intuition: The Continuity Thesis," "Things in Themselves: The Historical Lessons" – Offprints, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Grene, Marjorie: "Sein und Zeit: A Prospective Retrospect" – Typescript, undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Guyer, Paul: Henrich and Broad Reviews – Offprints, "The Unity of Reason" – Typescript and Extracts, 1979, undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Guyer, Paul: "Kant's Intentions on the Refutation of Idealism," "Placing Myself in Time: Kant's Third Paradigm" – Typescript Draft, Photocopy, 1981, undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Guyer, Paul: "Kant's Tactics in the Transcendental Deduction" – Typescript Draft, Letter with comments, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Guyer, Paul: "Kant's Second Analogy: Object, Events, and Causal Laws," with extensive comments, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Guyer, Paul: Kant and the Claims of Knowledge – Bound Typescript [1 of 2], 1985 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Guyer, Paul:: Kant and the Claims of Knowledge – Bound Typescript [2 of 2], 1985 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Haack, Susan: "The Two Faces of Quine's Naturalism," "Rebuilding the Ship while Sailing on the Water" – Typescripts, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Hare, Peter H.: "Dewey, Rorty, and the Ubiquity of Language" – Typescript, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Harper, William L.: "Kant's Empirical Realism and the Distinction between Subjective and Objective Succession," Kant's Empirical Realism and the Second Analogy of Experience" – Photocopies, circa 1984 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Hill, David K.: "Dissecting Trajectories.. ., " "The Projection Argument in Galileo and Copernicus" – Photocopies, 1984-1988 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Hintikka, Jaakko – "On the Interpretation of de Interpretatione XII-XIII" – Journal, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Horstmann, Rolf Peter: "Space and Intuition as Geometry" – Photocopy, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Kirkland, Frank M.: "Apperception and Combination: Some Kantian Problems" – Typescript, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Korsgaard, Christine: "The Ethical Philosophy of Immanuel Kant" – Draft, Comments, letter, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Korsgaard, Christine: "Kant's Formulation of Universal Law" – Draft, Offprint, Correspondence, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Korsgaard, Christine: "Two Arguments Against Lying," "Morality as Freedom" – Typescript Drafts, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Korsgaard, Christine: "Kant's Formula of Humanity," "Skepticism About Practical Reason," "The Right to Lie: Kant on Dealing with Evil" –Offprints, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Korsgaard, Christine: "Kant's Analysis of Obligation: The Argument of Foundations I," "Introduction: Practical Foundations," Encyclopedia of Ethics Article – Drafts, 1988-1990 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Korsgaard, Christine: "Personal Identity and the Unity of Agency: A Kantian Response to Parfit": -- Typescript, Offprint, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Korsgaard, Christine: "Taking the Law into Our Own Hands.. .," "Normativity as Reflexivity.. .," "Creating the Kingdom of Ends.. ." Typescript Drafts, Notes, 1991, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Kyburg, Henry E. and Michael Pittarelli – "Some Problems for Convex Bayesians" – Photocopy, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Laserna, Mario: "From the Thalesian Flash to Critical Philosophy," On the Interpretation of Kantian Texts, Chapter 1 – Typescripts, 1986, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Lear, Jonathan: "Transcendental Anthropology" – Offprint, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Leary, David E.: "The Philosophical Development of the Conception of Psychology.. .," "The Intentions and Heritage of Descartes and Locke.. .," "Wundt and After.. .," "The Historical Foundation of Herbart's Mathematization of Psychology" – Offprints, Correspondence, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Lehe, Robert Tad: "Internal Realism and Truth," "Internal Realism and Reality" – Typescripts, Letter, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Linsky, Bernard: "Extensionality, Underdetermination, and Indeterminacy" – Typescript, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Linsky, Leonard: "The Unity of the Proposition," "Terms and Propositions in Russell's Principles of Mathematics," Janik/Toulmin Review – Offprints, 1975-1988 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Louden, Robert B.: "Kant's Virtue Ethics" – Offprint, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Malament, David B: "Why Space Must Be Euclidean" – Typescript, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Martin, Richard: "On the Language of Kantian Arithmetic" – Typescript, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - McInerny, Peter K.: "Kant on Subjective Succession and Time-Consciousness" – Typescript, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Meerbote, Rolf: "A Sometimes Neglected Aspect of Kant's Subjective Deduction" – Typescript, Letter, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Meerbote, Ralf: "Apperception and Objectivity," "Kant on Intuitivity," Review of Kitcher, Patricia, "Kant's Transcendental Psychology," 1981-1990 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Melnick, Arthur: "Kant on Intuition" – Offprint, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Melnick Arthur: "Kant's Conception of Thought" – Drafts, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Melnick, Arthur: Space, Time and Thought in Kant (Introduction, Table of Contents) – Typescript, Correspondence, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Mondadori, Fabrizio: "Reference, Essentialism, and Modality in Leibniz's Metaphysics" – Photocopy, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Mosser, Kurt: "Stuff and Nonsense in Kant's First Critique" – Draft and Letter, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Parsons, Charles: "Kant's Philosophy of, Arithmetic" with Postscript, Correspondence, Comments, Typescript, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Parsons, Charles: "Realism and Underdetermination," "Mathematical Intuition" –Offprints, Photocopy, Letter, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Parsons, Charles: "Arithmetic and the Categories" – Typescript, Offprint, Letter with Comments, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - O'Brien, George Dennis – Notes at the Margin, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Pastin, Mark: "Philosophy of Perception," "Warrant and Meaning in Quine's Clothing," "Knowledge and Reliability.. ." Typescript, Photocopies, Letter, circa 1979 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Peirce/Ketner: Consequences of Mathematics – Draft with Comments [1 of 4], 1987 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Peirce/Ketner: Consequences of Mathematics – Draft with Comments [2 of 4], 1987 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Peirce/Ketner: Consequences of Mathematics – Draft with Comments [3 of 4], 1987 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Peirce/Ketner: Consequences of Mathematics – Draft with Comments [4 of 4], 1987 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Thompson, Manley: Review of Peirce/Ketner Consequences of Mathematics – Correspondence, Draft, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Pippin, Robert: Prauss Reviews, Correspondence, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Putnam, Hilary: "Why Reason Can't Be Naturalized," "Why There Isn't a Ready-Made World" – Offprints, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Quine, W. V. O.: "On Empirically Equivalent Systems of the World," "Intensions Revisited," "Whither Physical Objects?" "Use and Its Place in Meaning" – Offprints, Photocopies, Memo, 1975-1979 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Ricoeur, Paul – "The Question of Proof in Freud's Psychoanalytic Writings" – Photocopy, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Robinson, Hoke: "The Priority of Inner Sense," "All or Nothing in Objective Judgment" – Drafts, Offprint, Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Robinson, Hoke: "Inner Sense and the Leningrad Reflexion, "Kant Translation, Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Roth, Paul A.: "Semantics Without Foundations" – Typescript, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Scheffler, Israel: "The Wonderful World of Goodman" – Photocopy, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Sedgwick, Sally: "Hegel's Critique of the Subjective Idealism of Kant's Ethics," "Can Kant's Ethics Survive the Feminist Critique?" – Typescript, Offprint, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Sedgwick, Sally: "On the Way to Objective Idealism.. .," "Hegel's Strategy and Critique of Kant's Mathematical Antinomies" – Typescripts, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Sedgwick, Sally: "Hegel on Kant's Antimonies and Distinction between General and Transcendental Logic," "O lying and the Role of content in Kant's Ethics" – Typescript, Offprints, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Sedgwick, Sally: "The Conditioned Formalism of General Logic in the Critique of Pure Reason," "Pippin on Hegel's Critique of Kant" – Typescripts, Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Sellars, Wilfrid: "Mental Events," "On Reasoning About Values" – Offprints, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Sellars, Wilfrid: "Towards a Theory of Predication" – Typescript, undated (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Sellars, Wilfrid: "Mental Events" – Offprint, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Shapere, Dudley – "Newton," "Newtonian Mechanics" (Encyclopedia of Philosophy) – Tear Sheets, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Shapere, Dudley – "The Character of Scientific Change" – Typescript, Comments, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Shwayder, David – "An Elementary Treatise on Metaphysics" – Correspondence, Comments, Referee Report, 1974-1981 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Shwayder, David – "On the Determination of Reference by Sense" – Offprint, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Simon, Herbert A.: "The Computer as a Laboratory for Epistemology" – Photocopy, Correspondence, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Simon, Herbert A.: "Black Ravens and a White Shoe" – Typescript, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Singer, Milton: "The Semiotics of Indian Identity" – Photocopy, Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Stern, Josef: "Metaphor and Grammatical Deviance," "metaphor Without Mainspring" – Offprints, 1983-1988 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Sternfeld, Robert, and Harold Zyskind: "Plato's Parmenides and the Transcendental Conditions of Discourse" –Photocopy, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Streeter, Robert E.: "WASPs and Other Endangered Species," 1977 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Synthese – Index to Volumes 1-17, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Tait, William W. – Critical Review of Charles Parsons' Mathematics in Philosophy – Typescript, Offprint, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Tate, John – Untitled Paper – Draft, Comments, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Thompson, Manley: Review of Ketner and Cook: Charles Sanders Peirce: Contributions to the Nation – Typescript, Correspondence, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Thompson, Manley: Review of Hilary Putnam, Reason, Truth, and History – Typescripts, circa 1981 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Thompson, Manley: Review of Skagestad, Peter, The Road of Inquiry –Offprints, Correspondence, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Thompson, Manley: Review of Ameriks, Karl: Kant's Theory of Mind – Typescript, Correspondence, 1982-1985 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Toulman, Stephen: "The Inwardness of Mental Life," 1979 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Valberg, Jerry – "Necessary Truth" – Typescript, Correspondence, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Vlastos, Gregory, "The Socratic Elenchus," "Afterthoughts.. .' – Photocopies, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Walker, Ralph C. S.: "A Selective Bibliography on Kant," 1978 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Wedin, Michael – "Aristotle on the Mind's Self-motion" – Typescript, Letter, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - White, Morton: "Why Annalists of Ideas Should Be Analysts of Ideals" – Offprint, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Wieand, Jeffrey, "Can there be an Institutional Theory of Art?" – Offprint, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Wilson, Kirk Dallas: "Kant on Intuition," "Studies in the Formal Logic of Kant's Modal Functions of Judgment" – Offprints, 1975-1978 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Young, J. Michael: "Kant's View of Imagination," "Kant on the Construction of Arithmetical Concepts" – Offprint, Photocopy, 1982-1988 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Young, J. Michael: "Synthesis and the Content of Concepts," "Objectivity, Universality, and the Content of Kant's First Critique" – Typescripts and Correspondence, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Zeman, Jay: "Generalized Normal Logic," Foulis and Randall "Operational Statistics I" – Offprint and Photocopy, circa 1978 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Zeman, Jay and Enid Wetherell: "Gestalt Work as Adaptive Inquiry" – Typescript, Correspondence, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Series VII: Oversize
  - Clippings – Speed Limit, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Los Angeles Daily Journal – Bakke Opinion, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - The Chronicle of Higher Education – Bakke Articles, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Series VIII: Restricted
  - ACLS Grant – Andy Reath – Letters of Support, Correspondence, Papers (R-30), 1984-1986 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Grant Recommendations – Henry Allison (R-30), 1984-1991 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Guyer: Kant and the Claims of Knowledge – Review and Correspondence (R-25), 1985 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Kant's Mathematics – Unfinished Manuscript (Senate Council Minutes on Reverse) (R-30), 1985-1986 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Eckart Fӧrster NEH Grant Review – Correspondence, Review Materials (R-30), 1986 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Grant Recommendations – Michael Friedman (R-30), 1986 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Reviewer Reports (R-30), 1986-1990 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - NEH Grant Review – Karl Ameriks – Application, Review, Correspondence, (R-30), 1987 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - NEH Grant Review – Alan R. Mabe – Application, Correspondence, review (R-30), 1988 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - NEH Grant Review – John Michael Young – Application, Correspondence, Review (R-30) 1988 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Postscript to "Singular Terms and Intuitions in Kant's Epistemology" (Faculty Senate Council Minutes on Reverse) (R-30), 1989 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Alan Donagan – Bellagio Residency Recommendation (R-25), 1990 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Humboldt Fellowship Recommendation Materials – Stephen Engstrom (R-25), 1990 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - NEH Grant Review – Robert Louden – Application, Correspondence (R-30), 1990 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - North American Kant Society – Conference Papers, Review Correspondence (R-25), 1990 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Harvard Visiting Committee – Correspondence and Reports (R-50), 1965-1976 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Hiring Recommendations (R-50), 1972-1974 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Hiring Recommendations (R-50), 1976-1978 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Hiring Recommendations (R-50), 1979-1984 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - NY State Doctoral Project – Rating Committee Reports (R-50), 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Harvard University Overseers Visiting Committee – Reports, Correspondence, Review Materials (R-50), 1980-1982 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Recommendations – Paul Guyer (R-50), 1981-1983 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Harvard University Overseers Visiting Committee – Reports, Correspondence, Review Materials (R-50) [1 of 2], 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Robinson, Hoke Tenure Review Materials, Correspondence (R-50), 1985 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Eckart Fӧrster Reappointment Review – Correspondence, Articles, C.V. (R-50), 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Hiring Recommendations (R-50), 1985-1989 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Stephen Engstrom Dossier Letter (R-50), 1989 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Eckart Fӧrster Tenure Review – Correspondence, C.V., Articles (R-50), 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Henry Allison Tenure Review – Materials and Correspondence (R-50), 1990 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Letters of Recommendation/Reference – Sally Sedgwick (R-50), 1991 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Thompson – Student Paper, Note to Russell (R-80), 1939 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Thompson – Student Paper with Comment, Postcard (R-80), 1939-1940 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Evaluative Correspondence re Student (R-80), circa 1960 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Recommendations – Zeman, J. Jay (R-80), 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Seminars on Kant's Dialectic – Class Lists, Grades, Student Correspondence (R-80), 1977-1985 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Student Recommendations (R-80), 1980-1985 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Paul Roth -- Recommendation (R-80), 1981 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Recommendations – Heisook Kim (R-80), 1982-1987 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Letters of Recommendation – Sally Sedgwick (R-80), 1982-1988 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Letters of Recommendation – Godlove, Terry (R-80), 1982-1991 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Phil 475: Kant's Critique of Pure Reason: Grade Lists, Evaluative Correspondence (R-80), 1983-1988 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Evaluative Letters – Amy Petullo (R-80), 1984 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Letters of Recommendation/Statements of Support – Stephen Engstrom (R-80), 1984-1986 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Recommendations and Evaluations – Kurt Mosser (R-80), 1984-1991 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Student Correspondence – Pamela Lau (R-80), 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Student Recommendations (R-80), 1986-1990 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Wang Wing-Chun – Papers and Comments (R-80), 1990 (Box 27, Folder 7)